



SUMMARY

As a former system administrator with a passion for technology, I am currently pursuing a career in software development. I am enrolled in a Software Development program and self-learning at the same time to gain skills and knowledges base on the industry trend. I actively participate in tech gatherings and hackathon activities to engage with the market and earn valuable experiences from senior developers. I am currently working on a project with my team to build a WebApp for my client. This is a real business solution and I will be involved to go through the entire software development lifecycle with agile methodology. I mastered Java and C# for object-oriented programming, and I also used to implement JavaScript and React framework for frontend development. For database connections, I have experiences to work on either SQL or NoSQL. I am familiar with data structures & algorithms so I am able to analyze and improve a project's performance.

In my previous job, I was responsible for User Acceptance Testing so I am confident for workflow of software development life cycle and how to perform effective testing to a system. As a team player, I am highly motivated and proactive to learn and cooperate with senior colleagues in the team, which will enable me to contribute effectively to the team's success.

EDUCATION

Diploma of Software Development | Southern Alberta Institute of Technology (SAIT) | 2022 – present **Bachelor of Supply Chain Management** | Hang Seng University of Hong Kong | 2012 – 2016

WORK EXPERIENCES

ERP System Administrator | Hospital Authority | Nov 2018 – Aug 2022

- Software testing & development assisting
 - Wrote testing script and performed User Acceptance Test for system update and newly deployed software;
 system post-maintenance possibility reduced by 36.6%, resulting in US\$ 0.76M in annual cost-savings
 - Managed projects on mobile applications development including UI/UX design for procurement department to streamline and enhance the procure-to-pay workflow; projects shortened down procurement lead time by 58.6% and procurement department increased Key Performance Index (KPI) by 22% in satisfying hospital needs
 - Prepared technical documentation for software version control and maintain a smooth work task hand-over for new stakeholders
- Helpdesk for ERP system
 - Acted as tier 2 helpdesk for frontline user with enquiry in Oracle ERP system; up to 600 general enquiries unrelated to system issue were answered per month before being escalated to tier 1 development team so the team's work efficiency was increased by 24.3%
 - Replicated system issues from users and reported to development team, facilitating communication and pushing problem solving process faster 1.5 times than before

Procurement Officer | Hospital Authority | Aug 2017 – Nov 2018

- Conducted tender exercise for medical equipment and consumables to comply with public hospital needs; user satisfaction level increased by 24%
- Managed customer relationship with medical vendors to stand by for public hospital's emergency plan; at least 50 urgent cases were solved annually with vendors providing supplies
- Controlled inventory level of medical supplies; out of stock situation was reduced to 6%

Logistics Executive | Miniso | Dec 2016 – Aug 2017

Quality Analyst Intern | State Grid | Jul 2015 – Aug 2015

SKILLS

Tech Stack: JavaScript, React, React Native, Java, C#, Python, SQL, HTML, CSS, Git, Azure

Language: English, Chinese – Mandarin & Chinese – Cantonese

VOLUNTEERING